It all started with a single statement from Elma.
I demand improved working conditions!
What's this about? Are you hangry?
This company wants too much overtime, and you know it!
The workload required of each individual is absolutely...
It's not that Elma's demands were unjustified.
We just didn't have a say in our scheduling.
Plus, our company's already made some solid improvements since its founding.
It took some time, but the working conditions have improved.
And compared to how things used to be, the amount of work seems like a fair exchange.
I tried to explain this to her, but...
You can't just give up and accept this abuse!
I refuse to give in!
I'm gonna fight for our freedom!
Surrounded by those of us who had grown accustomed to exploitative labor
and living out our days aimlessly, Elma took a stand all by herself.
Good luck!
Two days later, Elma used the few moments she had in between assignments to create a proposal for improved working conditions.
I was once again astonished by how capable dragons could be.
However...
You're laughing at me!
You want to expand personnel?
Yes!
We're currently doing mid-career recruitment and there's not a single applicant.
Why's that?
Because of the programming language we're expected to use at this company.
Even if we hired new grads, they'd still need a training period.
But they'd catch up quickly, right?
Not everyone is like you.
Here you go.
Try again taking all that into account.
I finished the revisions!
That was fast!
I was surprised by her speed, but it was the content that really left me shocked.
The rough spots had been completely revised.
None of the sections had any contradictions, and the text was organized perfectly.
This is great!
You mean that?
Submit it to our department head right away.
I'm on it!
It's a no-go.
He gave her some babble about the company's income and expenditures.
Things programmers don't even deal with.
And she couldn't fight back.
I could tell she was getting emotional about it, so I hit her with one of these.
Damn it!
I revised it again!
There's something wrong with you!
We were all overwhelmed by Elma's intensity as we began reading through the latest draft.
It was epic.
She had listed every individual's schedule in detail, including bathroom breaks, midday fatigue,
time away from workspaces, and even the amount of time resting their heads on their elbows
or recrossing their legs.
It was laid out like a curse disguised as a proposal to improve efficiency.
It was a testament to our complete lack of privacy that many employees felt it would have been more humane
for our boss to publish nude photos of them on the company website without their permission.
How did she get all this information?
According to her...
I used my clairvoyance.
I made my vision a thousand-screen multi-display.
Even her analogies were being influenced by work.
She triumphantly headed to submit her proposal again.
Shocking content aside, it was thorough and convincing enough to serve in negotiations.
Maybe half-day Fridays could be more than just a dream.
Still, it could be trauma bonding, but I don't know how I'll be able to relax if I don't work at least eight hours.
That's sad.
However, the dream was only alive for a short time.
All three of us were surprised when we were summoned by the executive director.
He wasn't going to fire us, was he?
We headed to his office with anxiety on our faces and terror in our hearts.
Come in.
It's us!
Hey.
I hear you've been very kind to Shota.
Oh, no.
That's Shota Baby's father.
Isn't he a mage or something?
Did you have a look at the improvement proposal?
Yes.
You did a very good job on it overall.
Joey Elma, right?
Forgive me.
Would you prefer Priestess of the Holy Seas?
Huh?
I'm currently an employee here, so whichever you prefer.
Would you mind telling us what this is all about?
Honestly, it's about the goddess Shota summoned.
See, I figured if you were her friends, then I should be familiar with you, too.
I bet she's ruining your son's education, isn't she?
What a perv.
She's also an ex-goddess.
We have a rule in our family that we take responsibility for our summons.
And contrary to your belief, I think the lady is good for Shota's education in many ways.
Be sure to thank her when he develops a fetish for older, questionable women.
All right, my friends.
I think now would be a good time to discuss business, yes?
That sucks.
I was hoping he'd go for it.
People would complain if he did.
It wouldn't be fair for only our department to improve.
He at least got that portion right.
Hey, I'm just glad he took the time to look it over.
I've noticed we've been getting out on time more frequently, so obviously he's taking some of it.
That doesn't matter!
It's not enough!
This company is an ethical nightmare, and it's up to us to turn it around!
Did that come out of you?
As you clutch your bag of hush money chocolates?
That is that, and this is this! Chocolates are low in sugar!
That doesn't make any sense.
Even after accepting his bribe, Elma refused to give up.
She tried to start a labor union on site.
She created a safe space for employee discussion and continued to advocate for better working conditions.
What surprised me most was that Toru was helping her with that.
I think it's a great plan, and if it works out, you'll be able to come home to me earlier!
It all makes sense now.
And if it doesn't work out, she'll...
Back at you!
Seeing rival forces cooperating for mutual benefit gave me hope that maybe it could work.
However, our executive director was crafty.
He used both logic and delusions in perfect ratios to sidestep every claim.
Damn it!
This is so unfair!
Elma, are you...
No, I'm not okay!
I shouldn't have to work so late and always miss the limited sweets!
That's what this is about?
I've finally finished work in enough time to experience those limited-time flavors!
It's a miracle!
Three of those, please!
Three of them!
Two, please!
I'll have two.
Uh, actually, just one's cool.
Thank you, beautiful human!
Bestie off ever!
I'll be doing nothing but eating delicious sweets!
Huh?
Hello?
What are you doing here?
We wanted to go on a picnic, but we're not allowed to go far alone.
We need an adult.
Where's Miss Kobayashi?
Oh, that's right.
She did say they were making her work today.
What about Toru?
She said this letter's for you.
Let's see.
Kana watched a survival show, and now she wants to go to the mountains and pretend to search for food.
I have to help out at the maid cafe today, so I can't go with her.
I was hoping maybe you would take her instead.
This means I do have some faith in you, so try to live up to it.
Oh, you have faith in me?
That condescending tone practically jumped off the page.
Okay, let's go.
The wilderness awaits!
Yay!
Good job!
You did it, Kana!
Let's set up our tent here.
Sorry.
We ran into Shota on our way to your house, and he asked to come to the mountains with us.
I'm glad he did.
So what are you two going to do now?
Fish.
We rented pools!
Fishing?
That takes me back.
Long ago, I was the one fished.
Okay, I'm bored.
That was pretty fast.
Is there a way we can speed these fish up?
Using our hands?
That might be more fun.
Why don't you try further down?
There are more fish in that area.
Look, we caught one!
Yeah, I think that's where I would have hidden, too.
Hit for what?
The curry and rice are ready, too.
Yay!
Chaperoning children isn't as hard as I thought.
This curry's good.
Thank you for the meal.
That's a neat bug, Cyclone.
Ew, gross!
They seem to be having fun.
I'm going to go relax a bit.
Shotao, where are you going?
Research.
I've been doing a lot of reading lately about how to draw mana from the ley lines.
They're supposed to be especially strong in the mountains.
That sounds like fun.
I want to go, too.
Why the boys of the West?
No!
There's no way.
They were just here.
How did I lose them?
They disappeared the moment I took my eyes off of them.
I don't want to hear it!
Wow.
You couldn't handle taking them on a picnic?
So lame.
No!
That's right.
I completely forgot I have clairvoyance.
I'll find them in no time.
What's wrong, Shota?
Someone just tried to hone in on us from a distant location.
I'm sure it was Lukua.
She does that sometimes.
But I blocked it.
Oh, you boys sure are silly.
That's weird.
Why can't I sense them?
I never should have relied on you to do anything.
Too bad.
Lame.
You guys!
Come on.
We should get back soon.
If it gets dark, it's possible we could lose our way.
Oh, we're fine.
Chill.
We followed the ley lines out here.
We can just trace them again to get back.
You boys.
Actually, we left without saying anything to Miss Elma.
We should get back soon.
Did either of you hear that scream just now?
Someone may have seen a bear.
Okay, we made it.
That's weird.
She's not here.
Did she get mad and go home because we left without telling her?
She might have been worried and gone out to look for us.
Damn it!
Where could they be?
You idiot!
Well before me.
So useless.
I keep hearing Toru saying mean things to me in my head.
Hi, excuse me.
I'm looking for someone.
Have you seen any children around here?
There are three of them.
How rude.
Do you want to be eaten?
If it's not one thing, it's another.
Where could they be?
Please!
I'm looking!
Connor, look!
That's the one I saw in the river that time!
Lady Elma, down here!
We're sorry.
You know you worried me.
Yes.
Lady Elma, for you.
That's a pretty flower.
I picked it for you.
It's yours.
I hope you can forgive us.
Connor!
I want a flower too!
Where's Connor?
I forgive you!
So sweet!
So easy.
Oh man, thanks for the save.
I'm sorry I wasn't home to help you with all of that.
Don't worry about it.
The nectar from that flower was actually quite tasty.
You ate flower nectar?
It was the flower I picked.
Save it, Toru.
I will not let you call me pathetic or ridiculous.
As if I'd waste those words on you.
Here's your coffee.
Are you going to set out cake?
You're pushing it today.
Gotten hot lately, hasn't it?
Yeah, it's summer already.
Okay.
Ah-huh.
Ah!
Yeah!
Ordinarily, I'd never entertain a request from a Harmony Faction Dragon.
But I like your choice to rely on organic power.
I'll accept, in honor of that spirit, just this once.
You have my gratitude.
Today, we're here with the Mobile Zoo, appropriately named Zoo That Goes Anywhere.
Amazing.
The main attraction appears to be this adorable giraffe.
Coming!
What are you two doing here?
We were able to chat with the zoo director, Mr. Miyamoto.
It's unusual for Elma to ask Toru to go anywhere with her.
Much less something as casual as joining her for exercise because she's feeling rusty.
What's even weirder is that Toru seemed to genuinely accept the random invite.
Maybe the tension between them is finally ironing out?
I'm so glad they're getting along lately.
Elma's really softened up.
Don't be so naive.
There's a reason the two of us were called here today.
Why is that?
Toru!
Kobayashi, you decide when it's time for them to stop.
I'm soğıism.
There's a reason the thres she is sc трудed.
Okay.
Whichly is...
Whi'all are cute.
White.
Okay.
What?
Let's see.
They say fine.
What?
This is...
How is it happening?
This is false.
How is it?
What is it?
Who?
The...
How is it?
Who is it?
What is it?
We are poor.
what was that about getting rusty you're such a liar are you trying to settle things after all
this time if i win this fight will you return home with me to our world when will you let that go
you're dangerous you know that dangerous you've corrupted the hearts of humans huh
you're not making sense she may talk about harmony and wanting to provide guidance for mankind but
make no mistake it's only because of the faction she's in she's been used and betrayed somewhere
in her heart she holds contempt for humans in general that's the main reason she still sees
toru as an enemy i don't know if i believe that one faff what
i haven't even thought about doing anything wrong since i've been here and i don't plan on changing
that anytime soon all i did was make it feel free to talk to how can you say that while happily
working in a main cafe among hundreds of humans each day after so many times you swore you would
never trust them here you are serving them and all this after you ridiculed me for being worshipped
by humans in our original world not true it wasn't because of their love it was because you took
advantage of it you love being on a pedestal but you didn't want to join them
you think you look so noble not taking offerings made to you but it's only because you still buy them
yourself the food we have in our original world is much better than what we have here
what does that have to do with anything
it means it was better
then go go back on your own and leave me out of there
the reason it was better is because you were there beside me
you laughed without telling me do you know how worried i was the next thing i heard was that you
had died that's right then when i finally found you again you had changed and were blatantly cold to
me while developing meaningful friendships with humans i don't understand that's just
why would you throw a friendship like hours away you idiot
i'm sorry elma i truly mean that
but setting that fun fact aside
ow it's time we put this thing to rest
you got it brace yourself toru shut up you brace yourself i don't have time for this
i'm going home hey thanks for coming
the magic and horror of witnessing dragon battles isn't lost on me but i am pretty used to them now
i will say that this particular fight is reassuring to watch
toru
what do you want elma take me to dinner i won this
no you didn't you know it i won you take me
i'll take you both out
why are you happy about that
hey that's a draw
Ms. Kobayashi, can you tell us where we're going for dinner?
That depends on what you want to eat.
I want the highest grade beef!
You've learned the most useless things about our world.
This week on Who's Rotten?
Gemini.